Hey guys, I hope you are loving this so far
and the story is getting built step by step
and I hope you are taking down the notes.
You've got to be able
to have the story in your system right here.
When you have it here, you'll be able
to reproduce in your interviews without any hiccups at all.
If they cross question you, you can really talk about
what exactly you have done in your project,
and this is why I recommend that you note down all of that
and in the comments below,
in your own words, write your story.
This will reinforce things in your system.
Alright, the next step, okay, is gonna be very,
very important because now you have given the
data to the data analyst.
They're gonna analyze the data
and they are going to come up with the requirements
for the data engineering projects.
They're gonna tell exactly how they want the data
to be transformed from the raw to the curated,
where you'll transform the data
and curated, you'll move it to aggregated when you wanna,
when you wanna see the aggregated data, which they can use
to make business decisions, the revenue optimization
and the driver operations optimization.
So it requirements part is gonna be very, very critical.
Okay? Because when the interviewer asks you,
or even when the recruiter calls you
and asks you, do me a, tell me your roles
and responsibilities in the project, you will have
to talk about this, that I would be given the requirements
from the analyst team
and I would build my data engineering pipeline
based on the requirements.
Right? Before we go to the next video,
make sure you type down your story in your own words
below the video, and also read
others' comments as well, right?
See how they are interpreting it Dr. Soon.